New York State Tenants and Neighbors, Inc; Records apap198
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Audio Visual Materials, 1973-2000, Undated; 6; 1.5 cubic ft.
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: The Sublet Guide # 12/24, 2000 August (Video-tape 11)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: A Bounty on Tenants Heads # 35, 2000 October (Video-tape 12)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Pitaki's Sneak Attack on Tenants # 36, 2000 November (Video-tape 13)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: The Lead Law: A Year Later # 37, 2000 November (Video-tape 14)
  - Dangers of Primary Residence Decontrol, 2001 January (Video-tape 15)
  - Pataki Trashes Tenant Rights, 2001 February 01 (Video-tape 16)
  - The High Income Decontrol Trap, 2001 Febraury (Video-tape 1)
  - Tenants & Neighbors, 2001 May 02 (Video-tape 2)
  - Owner Use Eviction, 2001 July 03 (Video-tape 3)
  - Rent 2002 Campaign, 2001 December 14 (Video-tape 4)
  - Tenant Association Meeting in Washington D.C., 2002 June (Video-tape 5)
  - Rally March, 2002 June (Video-tape 6)
  - 90 Days- Documentary, Undated (Video-tape 7)
  - "Hot Line" # 1 with Sam Himmelstein, Undated (Video-tape 8)
  - Leo House Tenants Evicted- The Fight Continues, Undated (Video-tape 9)
  - PBS Frontline- Other Peoples Money, Undated (Video-tape 10)
  - Rent Guidelines Hearing, Undated (Video-tape 11)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: # 29, 2000 March (Video-tape 1)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Mitchell- Llama Fights Back # 30, 2000 April (Video-tape 2)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Rent 2000: Victory for Tenants # 31, 2000 May (Video-tape 3)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: HUD Tenants Getting it Together # 32, 2000 June (Video-tape 4)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Renting and Raving # 33, 2000 July (Video-tape 5)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: The Sublet Guide # 12/24, 2000 August (Video-tape 6)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: Pitfalls of Subletting # 35, 2000 September (Video-tape 7)
  - The Tenants & Neighbors Show: The Lead Law: A Year Later # 37, 2000 December (Video-tape 8)
- National Housing Issues, 1973-2000, Undated; 7; 1.8 cubic ft.
  The National Housing Issues series is arranged chronologically.
  The National Housing Issues series focuses on renters' issues from a national perspective. Much of the materials come from the National Alliance of HUD Tenants as well as the Low Income Housing Information Service.
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development- Title 24, Chapter IV, Part 403 Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 1)
  - National Committee for Rent Control - Fact Sheets, 1978 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 2)
  - National Housing Law Project- Security Deposit Packet, 1980 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 3)
  - Washington, D.C. Housing Statistics, Uniformed Planned Community Act, 1980 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Zone Legislation and U.S. Congressman Jack Kemp- Housing Resolutions, 1980-1983 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 5)
  - National Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Materials, 1980-1988 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 6)
  - National Housing Law Project- Legislative Update on House Authorization Bill, 1983 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 7)
  - Low Income Housing Information Service, 1983-1993 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 8)
  - Low Income Housing Information Service, 1984-1993 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 9)
  - Housing at Risk: Expiring Federal Subsidies, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 10)
  - Housing at Risk: Expiring Federal Subsidies, 1988 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 11)
  - National Housing Law Project: State and Local Iniatives to Preserve Subsized Rental Housing, 1988 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 12)
  - Northeast States: Proposals on Federal Incentives Needed to Preserve Assisted Housing, 1989 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 13)
  - Community Service Society- Papers on National Housing Issues, 1990 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 14)
  - Congressional Record- House, 1990 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 15)
  - HUD Tenant Alerts, 1990; Undated (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 16)
  - Low Income Housing Information Service- Pamphlets, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 17)
  - National Affordable Housing Act- Agency Questions, 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 18)
  - National Affordability Housing Act- Supprt Materials, 1992; Undated (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 19)
  - On Your Mark, Get Set, Take Control: A Guide for Residents About the First Nine Months of the Title 6 Program, 1993 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 20)
  - National Housing and Urban Developments- National Low Income Housing Coalition, 1994-1997 (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 21)
  - NYS Tenants & Neighbors Coalition National Memoranda, 1995; Undated (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 22)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 1997 July (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 23)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 1997 August (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 24)
  - Report on S. 462 the Public Housing Reform & Responsibility Act of 1997, 1997 August (Box 1 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 25)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 1997 September (Box 2 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 1)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 1997 October (Box 2 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 2)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 1997 November- December (Box 2 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 3)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 1999 January-March (Box 2 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 4)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 1999 April-June (Box 2 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 5)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 1999 July-August (Box 2 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 6)
  - Memo to Members: The Weekly Newsletter of the National Low Income Housing Coalition, 1999 September-December (Box 2 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 7)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 1999 September-December (Box 3 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 1)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 2000 January-March (Box 3 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 2)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 2000 April-August (Box 3 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 3)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants- Nassau County, 2000 April-December (Box 3 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 4)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 2000 September-December (Box 3 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 5)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 2001 January-April (Box 3 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 6)
  - National Alliance of HUD Tenants, 2001 May-August (Box 3 (7-National Housing Issues), Folder 7)
- News Clippings, 1973-2000, Undated; 8; 0.4 cubic ft.
  The News Clippings series is arranged chronologically.
  The News Clippings series represents Tenants & Neighbors voice in the press. Much of it is Op Ed pieces written by Michael McKee. The bulk of the materials is from 1997, focusing on rent decontrol. Various rent protest and rallies that Tenants & Neighbors participated in or organized are also found in this series.
  - News Clippings, 1970-1991 (Box 1 (8-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1992-1996 (Box 1 (8-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1997 (Box 1 (8-News Clippings), Folder 3-4)
  - News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (8-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (8-News Clippings), Folder 6)